avantlink.com 2019-12-31

# AvantLink - Privacy Policy

## Privacy

#### Your privacy is important to you - and us. Here are our policies.

Dynamic Web Source, Inc. dba Avant Marketing Group (“AvantLink”) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. We collect, retain, protect and, in some instances, disclose information about you in connection with the operation of this website (the “Site”) and our affiliate marketing products and services (the “Network”). The Site and the Network are referred to as the “Service”.

This notice explains our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using the Site, or affiliating with the Network, either as an Affiliate or Merchant, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy and you are consenting to the practices outlined herein. Some terms used in this Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms of Use. 

**Overview**

  * We collect personal information from users of our Service that identifies you as a person when it is voluntarily provided by you through our Site, such as your name and email address (see **Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service** below).
    * This information is used to contact you about our Service, manage your account and other purposes described below.
  * We automatically collect browsing information and other information from users of our Service that does not identify you as a person, such as information to track, validate and report on a purchase through the Network or browsing activity on the Site (see **Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service** below).
    * This information is used to verify sales through our Network and to ensure Affiliates and Merchants get proper credit for their activities. In these situations, we are acting as a service provider to the Affiliates and Merchants.
  * We also use all of this information for our internal purposes, such as improving and managing our Services, fraud detection, security and similar uses (see **Our Use of Information** below).
  * You can access, delete and control certain uses of your information (see **User Rights - Data Access and Opt-Out** below).

**1\. Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service**

_Website_ : In order to register as an Affiliate or Merchant, Users are required to provide contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), payment details and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity to access our Services. Other information is provided to verify your identity and allow for proper communications and business dealings between the Network, Affiliates and Merchants.

_Network_ : In connection with use of our Network, and the availability of links through our Network, we may automatically collect information such as a device's IP address or mobile device ID, browsing activity and similar information which indicates how a user has interacted with our Network, Affiliates or Merchants. 

**2\. Our Use of Information**

We may use your information as follows.

  * to operate the Service and deliver the products and services you have requested.
  * to track, validate and report on activity through links for Affiliates and Merchants in the Network.
  * to detect, prevent and respond to fraudulent activities.
  * to inform you of other products or services available from AvantLink. 
  * to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. 
  * otherwise with your consent or consistent with the foregoing uses.

**3\. Sharing of your information**

We may share your information with third parties as follows:

  * with trusted vendors and service providers, such as payment processors and hosting providers. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to AvantLink, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
  * when required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with legal process served on AvantLink; (b) comply with requests of law enforcement; or (c) protect and defend the rights or property of AvantLink or third parties.
  * in connection with a merger, sale, reorganization or bankruptcy involving AvantLink.

**4\. Cookies**

We also collect and store certain types of information when you interact with us by using “cookies” and logs, which are tools that obtain information from your Internet device as you access AvantLink and/or our ad campaign tracking system. These cookies are used to help us improve your user experience and to track, validate and report on Affiliate, Merchant and user activity through the Service and the links. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your device or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

**5\. User Rights - Data Access and Opt-Out**

We provide you with choices regarding the Information you provide to us.

  * _Personal Information_ -
    * _Delete / Modify / Copy_ \- If you would like to delete, modify or receive a copy of your personal information, you may contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com).
    * _Categories & Information_ \- If you would like to receive the categories of personal information collected about you, the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected, the purpose for collecting the personal information, the categories of third parties which whom we share the personal information and the specific pieces of personal information collected about you, then you may contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com).
    * We do not sell your personal information to third parties for their own use (except in connection with a merger, sale, reorganization or bankruptcy involving AvantLink).
    * _Emails_ \- If you have signed up to receive our marketing e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Service, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Service.
    * _Cookies_ \- You may delete or block cookies and other technologies by following the instructions above.

We will need to validate any request to exercise these rights, including any authorized agent.

  * _EU Data Subject Rights._ If you are a situated in the EU, under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), as a data subject, you have the following rights:
    * _Legal basis_ \- We will only process your personal data with your consent, where we have a legitimate interest in doing so, in order to perform a contract or in order to meet a legal obligation.
    * _Right to access_ \- This right allows individuals to obtain confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her is being process and provide access to such personal data. It also allows individuals to request details of the processing of his or her personal data, including, without limitation, categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed and purposes of processing. 
    * _Right to rectify_ \- This right allows individuals to rectify any inaccurate personal data about him or her.
    * _Right to restrict processing_ \- This right allows individuals to block or suppress processing of personal data under certain circumstances.
    * _Right to be forgotten_ \- This right is also known as the “right to erasure”. It is an individual's right to have personal data erased or to prevent processing in specific circumstances.
    * _Right of data portability_ \- This right allows individuals to move, copy or transfer personal data from one place to another in a secure manner without interrupting the integrity and usability of the information.
    * _Right to object to processing_ \- This right allows individuals to object to certain types of processing, including direct marketing, profiling and providing for purposes of scientific or historical research and statistics.

Additionally, if we rely on consent for the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To exercise your rights under the GDPR, please contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com). If you are situation in the EU and have any complaints regarding our privacy practices, you have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authorities.

**6\. Children**

This Service is not intended for users under the age of 13 and do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**7\. Security; Data Retention**

In order to maximize the protection of your information, AvantLink uses industry standard technology to protect your information from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your information and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Your information is protected through reasonable and appropriate security measures, including but not limited to logical access restrictions, physical hardware and security restrictions, network restrictions, system access restrictions, and the principle of least privilege.

**8\. Amendments**

AvantLink reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy to keep up with new laws and regulations or if we determine that amendments are required for other reasons. The date of the latest amendment will be posted at the bottom of this policy.

**9\. General**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the AvantLink Terms of Use.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of the Service, please contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com)

Last Amended: November 20, 2019

Dynamic Web Source, Inc. dba Avant Marketing Group (“AvantLink”) has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. We collect, retain, protect and, in some instances, disclose information about you in connection with the operation of this website (the “Site”) and our affiliate marketing products and services (the “Network”). The Site and the Network are referred to as the “Service”.

This notice explains our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using the Site, or affiliating with the Network, either as an Affiliate or Merchant, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy and you are consenting to the practices outlined herein. Some terms used in this Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms of Use. 

**Overview**

  * We collect personal information from users of our Service that identifies you as a person when it is voluntarily provided by you through our Site, such as your name and email address (see **Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service** below).
    * This information is used to contact you about our Service, manage your account and other purposes described below.
  * We automatically collect browsing information and other information from users of our Service that does not identify you as a person, such as information to track, validate and report on a purchase through the Network or browsing activity on the Site (see **Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service** below).
    * This information is used to verify sales through our Network and to ensure Affiliates and Merchants get proper credit for their activities. In these situations, we are acting as a service provider to the Affiliates and Merchants.
  * We also use all of this information for our internal purposes, such as improving and managing our Services, fraud detection, security and similar uses (see **Our Use of Information** below).
  * You can access, delete and control certain uses of your information (see **User Rights - Data Access and Opt-Out** below).

**1\. Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service**

_Website_ : In order to register as an Affiliate or Merchant, Users are required to provide contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), payment details and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity to access our Services. Other information is provided to verify your identity and allow for proper communications and business dealings between the Network, Affiliates and Merchants.

_Network_ : In connection with use of our Network, and the availability of links through our Network, we may automatically collect information such as a device's IP address or mobile device ID, browsing activity and similar information which indicates how a user has interacted with our Network, Affiliates or Merchants. 

**2\. Our Use of Information**

We may use your information as follows.

  * to operate the Service and deliver the products and services you have requested.
  * to track, validate and report on activity through links for Affiliates and Merchants in the Network.
  * to detect, prevent and respond to fraudulent activities.
  * to inform you of other products or services available from AvantLink. 
  * to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. 
  * otherwise with your consent or consistent with the foregoing uses.

**3\. Sharing of your information**

We may share your information with third parties as follows:

  * with trusted vendors and service providers, such as payment processors and hosting providers. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to AvantLink, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
  * when required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with legal process served on AvantLink; (b) comply with requests of law enforcement; or (c) protect and defend the rights or property of AvantLink or third parties.
  * in connection with a merger, sale, reorganization or bankruptcy involving AvantLink.

**4\. Cookies**

We also collect and store certain types of information when you interact with us by using “cookies” and logs, which are tools that obtain information from your Internet device as you access AvantLink and/or our ad campaign tracking system. These cookies are used to help us improve your user experience and to track, validate and report on Affiliate, Merchant and user activity through the Service and the links. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your device or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

**5\. User Rights - Data Access and Opt-Out**

We provide you with choices regarding the Information you provide to us.

  * _Personal Information_ -
    * _Delete / Modify / Copy_ \- If you would like to delete, modify or receive a copy of your personal information, you may contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com).
    * _Categories & Information_ \- If you would like to receive the categories of personal information collected about you, the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected, the purpose for collecting the personal information, the categories of third parties which whom we share the personal information and the specific pieces of personal information collected about you, then you may contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com).
    * We do not sell your personal information to third parties for their own use (except in connection with a merger, sale, reorganization or bankruptcy involving AvantLink).
    * _Emails_ \- If you have signed up to receive our marketing e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Service, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Service.
    * _Cookies_ \- You may delete or block cookies and other technologies by following the instructions above.

We will need to validate any request to exercise these rights, including any authorized agent.

  * _EU Data Subject Rights._ If you are a situated in the EU, under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), as a data subject, you have the following rights:
    * _Legal basis_ \- We will only process your personal data with your consent, where we have a legitimate interest in doing so, in order to perform a contract or in order to meet a legal obligation.
    * _Right to access_ \- This right allows individuals to obtain confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her is being process and provide access to such personal data. It also allows individuals to request details of the processing of his or her personal data, including, without limitation, categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed and purposes of processing. 
    * _Right to rectify_ \- This right allows individuals to rectify any inaccurate personal data about him or her.
    * _Right to restrict processing_ \- This right allows individuals to block or suppress processing of personal data under certain circumstances.
    * _Right to be forgotten_ \- This right is also known as the “right to erasure”. It is an individual's right to have personal data erased or to prevent processing in specific circumstances.
    * _Right of data portability_ \- This right allows individuals to move, copy or transfer personal data from one place to another in a secure manner without interrupting the integrity and usability of the information.
    * _Right to object to processing_ \- This right allows individuals to object to certain types of processing, including direct marketing, profiling and providing for purposes of scientific or historical research and statistics.

Additionally, if we rely on consent for the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To exercise your rights under the GDPR, please contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com). If you are situation in the EU and have any complaints regarding our privacy practices, you have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authorities.

**6\. Children**

This Service is not intended for users under the age of 13 and do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**7\. Security; Data Retention**

In order to maximize the protection of your information, AvantLink uses industry standard technology to protect your information from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your information and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Your information is protected through reasonable and appropriate security measures, including but not limited to logical access restrictions, physical hardware and security restrictions, network restrictions, system access restrictions, and the principle of least privilege.

**8\. Amendments**

AvantLink reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy to keep up with new laws and regulations or if we determine that amendments are required for other reasons. The date of the latest amendment will be posted at the bottom of this policy.

**9\. General**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the AvantLink Terms of Use.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of the Service, please contact us at [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com)

Last Amended: November 20, 2019

This privacy policy is intended to explain to you how we intend to collect, store and use your personal information and to inform you of your rights under the Privacy Act 1988 (as amended) ( **Act** ) and the **GDPR**.

This privacy policy is supplemental to the general privacy policy published on our website.

We adhere to the Australian Privacy Principles ( **APPs** ) set out in the Act as well as the principles set out in the GDPR. The APPs and GDPR regulate the manner in which organisations like ours can collect, use, keep secure and disclose personal information.

**1\. Definitions**

In this Privacy Policy:

**Act** means the Privacy Act 1988 (as amended) and includes all subordinate legislation made pursuant to it.

**APPs** means the Australian Privacy Principles set out in the Act, as amended from time to time.

**Affiliate** has the same meaning as in our terms of use published on the Website.

**GDPR** means the General Data Protection Regulation.

**Group Entity** means Dynamic Web Source (Australia) Pty Ltd ACN 168 681 525 ( **DWS** ), Dynamic Web Source, Inc., Dynamic Web Source (Canada), Inc. and any company which is a related entity within the meaning of the Corporations Act 2001 (Cth) to any of them.

**Merchant** has the same meaning as in our terms of use published on the Website.

**Personal Information** has the same meaning as that term is given in section 6 of the Act.

**We** includes DWS and The Group Entities.

**Website** means the “AvantLink” website located at URL <http://www.avantlink.com.au/> operated by Dynamic Web Source, Inc. or any other Group Entity and includes all pages on the Website, but does not include any website at any other URL, regardless of whether or not it is accessed via a link from the Website.

**2\. Collection Methods and Purposes**

We collect personal information about our clients, potential clients, employees, potential employees, contractors and others for legitimate business interests including:

  * to properly represent our clients and to carry out our business functions and activities;
  * provide accurate sales referral tracking;
  * fraud prevention;
  * network security.
  * is reasonably practicable for us to do so, we collect personal information directly from you by asking you for it. Sometimes we receive and collect personal information about you from third parties, for example from a recruitment firm (in respect of an application for employment). We may also collect personal information from publicly available sources. The kinds of personal information we collect may include:
  * your name, address, occupation, and contact information;
  * if you are applying for employment by us, opinions about you, including your business or professional experience;
  * information about a person's dealings with us, any Merchant or Affiliate, which may include financial records, bank account or credit card details, insurance policies, taxation information;
  * IP address, web browser and device information;
  * in some circumstances, your ABN.

Where possible, we de-identify the personal information we collect, store, use and disclose, However, it may not always be possible for us to provide our services to you or any entity associated with you if we do not collect, store, use and disclose your personal information as otherwise outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Cookies**

The Website may utilize "cookies" to collect information for legitimate business interests. The cookies are designed to help DWS and other Group Entities determine that a particular user had visited the Website previously, and save any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the Website. The cookies cannot retrieve any other data from a user's hard drive or obtain a user's e-mail address. If a user is simply browsing the Website, a cookie may be used to identify the user's browser as one that has visited the Website before.

DWS may also make use of memory-based cookies in support of authenticating the user of certain web applications. Similarly, if you are a registered user of a service provided or facilitated by DWS (and have a user ID and password), DWS or any Group Entity operating the Website may use cookies so that we can provide personalized information based on preferences you have indicated while using the Website. Although you have the ability to modify your browser to either accept all cookies, notify you when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize DWS services which require registration if you reject cookies.

**4\. Use and Disclosure**

We use personal information collected by us to enable us to conduct our business, to carry on our marketing activities and to comply with our legal obligations, and in particular to:

  * to enable us to verify your identity;
  * to maintain and develop our relationship with you;
  * to market our services including by providing you with information about Affiliate or Merchant opportunities or events which may be of interest to you;
  * to consider your application for employment by us;
  * to comply with our legal obligations;
  * for research, planning, service development, security or risk management.

Your personal information is treated by us as strictly private and confidential, and will not be disclosed by us except as outlined in this Privacy Policy unless:

  * you consent to such disclosure;
  * the disclosure is required in the course of providing our services to you (eg. we may disclose personal information to our platform partners for the purposes of establishing and maintaining affiliate program relationships);
  * the disclosure is to an external service provider on a confidential basis relating to the provision of financial or administrative services (eg. archive services);
  * the disclosure is to a third party recruitment firm in respect of your prospective employment by us;
  * the disclosure is required to enforce any contract that we have entered into with you;
  * the disclosure is in connection with the actual or proposed sale, merger or divestment of all or part of our business (whether or not any such transaction is completed); or
  * we are required to do so by law.

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purposes of marketing their products or services to you.

**5\. Overseas Disclosure**

We may disclose your personal information to entities located overseas in the following countries: United States of America, Canada

You consent to us disclosing your personal information to other Group Entities overseas:

Your personal information is treated by us as strictly private and confidential, and will not be disclosed by us except as outlined in this Privacy Policy unless:

  * if necessary to administer our relationship with you;
  * if the relevant Group Entity provides services to, or functions for us or on our behalf;
  * for transactional reasons; or
  * to comply with Australian and global regulatory requirements applying to DWS or any Group Entity (including to comply with requests for information received by overseas regulators).

**6\. Data Quality**

All reasonable steps will be taken by us to ensure that the personal information that we collect and hold is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If however, you become aware that any of the personal information we hold about you is not accurate, complete or up-to-date, please contact us via the contact details appearing in section 14 below to update or change your personal information.

**7\. Data Security**

All of our personnel are required to protect the confidentiality of your personal information, subject to this Privacy Policy.

We take reasonable steps to protect all information that we hold, including personal information, from misuse and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

We do this by, for example:

  * using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions, which encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet;
  * incorporating strong password encryption and strict access procedures;
  * restriction of access to personal information to staff members who require access in order to perform their role;
  * taking all reasonable steps to keep our premises secure;
  * providing appropriate and regular training to staff regarding this Privacy Policy and information handling practices.

We may hold your information in either electronic or hard copy form.

**8\. Access and Correction**

You have the right of access to your personal data at any time and may demand correction.

You have the right to object to this processing of personal information if you wish, however if you do not provide your personal information to us as requested we may not be able to provide our services to you.

If you are registered as an Affiliate or Merchant client, you may access your personal information via your account interface and modify/update the data yourself.

If additional help is needed to access, correct, modify, delete or block personal information, please email [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com) or write to the Privacy Officer at the PO Box address appearing in section 14 below.

**9\. Sensitive Information**

We do not collect, use or disclose sensitive information about you (such as race, ethnicity, religion, sexual preference, health or criminal record) unless it is related to the provision of our services to you or our client, you provide your consent or where it is allowed by law.

**10\. Destruction of Personal Information**

Personal information is destroyed or de-identified when it is no longer needed or when we are no longer required by law to retain it (whichever is the later).

You agree that we may de-identify or destroy your personal information:

  * 7 years after the termination of your relationship with us; or
  * if you are a prospective employee, immediately upon us determining that your application for employment by us is unsuccessful.

**11\. Privacy Policy Changes**

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post any updated Privacy Policy on this website. You should check this website periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current Privacy Policy.

**12\. Complaints Procedure**

If you believe that your privacy has been breached, please contact us using the contact information below and provide details of the incident so that we can investigate it. We will treat your complaint confidentially, investigate your complaint and aim to ensure that we contact you and that your complaint is resolved within a reasonable time (and in any event within the time required by the Act, if applicable).

**13\. Your Agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy**

By using our Website, registering as an Affiliate or Merchant, applying for employment by us and/or providing your personal information to us, you accept and agree to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of your personal information in the manner and for the purposes described in this policy.

We review our policies regularly and occasionally may need to change or update them. Any updated versions of this privacy policy will be posted on our website and will be effective from the date of posting.

This policy is was last updated on 20 November 2019.

**14\. DWS Privacy Officer**

For all queries regarding personal information and to access your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer by clicking here [privacy@avantlink.com](mailto:privacy@avantlink.com), or by writing to the Privacy Officer, Dynamic Web Source, PO Box 683351 Park City, UT 84068, United States of America.
